Mohammad Sadegh Shad

Iran



m.sadegh.sh@gmail.com



989360643405



linkedin.com/in/mohammad-sadegh-shad

Summary

I'm an experienced Full-stack developer with more than 8 years of experience in developing and deploying corporate websites and web services for government bodies and commercial organizations with strong proficiency in the back-end (ASP.NET Core / C#) and front-end (HTML5 / CSS3 / React.js / Redux / Bootstrap) development.

I'm also a rookie and enthusiastic in the field of Mobile application development using Java and Flutter.

Experience



Frontend Developer

Hooshmand Sazan Bin

Jun 2018 - Present (2 years 4 months +)

Bina is trying to build the first fully-featured HIS product in Iran. There are a few HIS solutions based on a prototype with a bunch of limitations. In Bina, we'll do our best to overcome these limitations and provide a best in class product for countrywide usage. Here in Bina, I'm responsible to tune the existing product frontend section with our client's requirements. We're also planning to start the development process of the next version which would be a major upgrade with tons of new features, performance improvements, and a much cleaner and more maintainable codebase.



🐶 Full Stack Web Developer

Parnian Group

Oct 2013 - Jun 2018 (4 years 9 months)

Parnian is a private solution provider based on Microsoft's technologies like SharePoint, Exchange, Dynamic CRM and etc. I've been working on several products/projects.

I was a core developer for the Letter Management System which was a part of our Office Automation (LMS, BPMS, DMS) solution. This product consists of three main sections they work together to make the letterwriting process easier using Microsoft Outlook's and OWA's add-in, Microsoft Exchange Server agent for message routing and metadata extraction, and an ASP.NET MVC based portal for Searching Letters, Permission Management, Organization Chart Management and much more... The last version of this product I've been working on comes with built-in multi-tenancy.

Also, I've been developing several SharePoint 2013 solutions consists of WebParts, Migration Tools, Branding Packages and etc using Visual Studio and SOM.



Junior .NET Developer

Farayan

Oct 2012 - Oct 2013 (1 year 1 month)

Farayan was a private small Software development company and I've been working as a junior level .NET Developer in several projects.

Unfortunately, I've heard that the company has been disbanded.



Entry Level .NET Developer

Islamic Azad University

Jan 2012 - Sep 2012 (9 months)

IAU is a private country-wide University and I've been working in the Quchan's branch for several months. I worked there as an entry-level .NET Developer in the IT department.

Education



Atrak Technical Institute

Bachelor's degree, Computer Software Engineering 2010 - 2012



Sama

Associate's degree, Computer Software Engineering 2008 - 2010



Mahmoudiye

High School Diploma, Computer Software Engineering 2006 - 2008

Licenses & Certifications



Triplebyte Certified Front End Engineer - Triplebyte

R9FFy6w

Skills

C# • .NET • React.js • Web Development • Design Patterns • OOP • Web Services • Database Design • Android Development • Web Design